







Total Experience: 9 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computers]

Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Current Designation: Drupal Module Lead

Current Company: Tech Mahindra

Current Location: Hyderabad / Secunderabad

Pref. Location: Hyderabad, Hyderabad

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Team Lead/Tech Lead

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Drupal, PHP, MySQL, Wordpress, GIT, Jenkins, Ajax, E-commerce, Drush, jQuery, PHP Storm, Acquia cloud, and the story of the property of the prop

Google cloud, Amazon cloud, drupal 8, drupal 7

Verified : L Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills | Projects | Work Authorization

Summary

Extensive experience of nearly 9 years in executing full life-cycle Drupal projects

Nearly 9 years of experience on PHP 7, Drupal 8 & 7, Wordpress 5, Symfony. Rich experience in using AJAX, jQuery, HTML5,
CSS3, SCSS, Magento and Woo commerce Gained international exposure by working for Suncorp bank, TAL insurance
customers in Australia, Sydney Skilled in overall software development life-cycle involving requirement analysis, system
study, designing, architecture, testing, programming, coding, de-bugging, defect management, status reporting &
documentation Led initiatives to increase accessibility awareness and advise business stakeholders, designers and
developers on accessibility standards; provided ongoing advise and consulting on accessibility Followed the project life cycle
methodology defined under the process framework; ensured that customer deadlines were met within project budgets
ldentified architectural improvements resulting in increased developer efficiency

Work Experience

Tech Mahindra as Drupal Module Lead Jan 2017 to Till Date

Drupal Module Lead, Drupal 8, Drupal 7, Wordpress, Core PHP, GIT & Bit bucket, Jenkins, Docker, PHP Storm, Symfony, Acquia, AWS, jQuery, HTML5, CSS3

Ray Business Technologies as Senior Developer Feb 2015 to Jan 2017

Drupal 7, Wordpress, Core PHP, GIT & Bit bucket, Jenkins

Ace Dezines as Senior Software Engineer Jan 2013 to Feb 2015

Drupal 7, Wordpress, Core PHP, GIT & Bit bucket, Jenkins

Zonup Technologies as Software Engineer Oct 2011 to Dec 2012

Drupal 7, Wordpress 4, jQuery, Ajax, HTML, CSS, Core PHP

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from JNTU College of Engineering, Kakinada in 2011

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

Drupal 8

1

Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
PHP 7.x			
MVC, Symfony, Restful Web services			
Drupal 7 & 8, WordPress 5			
Woo Commerce, Magento			
HTML5, CSS3, jQuery, AJAX			
MYSQL 5.0			
Google Cloud, AWS, Acquia Cloud			
Acquia Site Factory, Polaris, Apache Tomcat			
NGINX			
GIT, Bit Bucket			
EBS, PayPal, Authorize.net, CC Avenue			
Click a tell, Twilio			
Jenkins, Drush, Docker, PHP Storm			
Eclipse, Jira, Ubuntu, Google analytics			

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
english	Expert	✓	✓	✓
hindi	Expert	✓	✓	✓
telugu	Expert	✓	✓	✓

^ Back to Top

Projects

Project Title: Asteron Life Client: Suncorp Bank Nature of Employment: Full Time Project Location: Australia Role: Module Leader

Skill Used: Drupal, PHP, M/SQL, HTML, CSS, Role Description: Customer communication, Development & maintenance, Delivery, Deployment, Team management

Project Details: Asteron Life & Adviser connect Drupal 7 & 8

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: General Physically Challenged: No Countries: Australia Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Duration: May 2019 - May 2020 Onsite / Offsite: Onsite

Team Size: 5